<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <Resur.Update.Title>Resurreviewy Update</Resur.Update.Title>
  
  <Resur.Update.label>
2023/8/8(0.2.1.0):
*Add Xenotype

2023/07/10(0.2.0.1):
*Fixed a bug that prevented Resurreviewy from filling in holes when in an unconscious state

2023/05/23(0.2.0.0):
*B.E.P Race Core is required as a prerequisite mod, and common parts have been greatly reduced.
If you are using an earlier version, various data such as hairstyles and clothes have been lost.
If you need an older version, you can download the mod before the update by going to github from the mod page.

2023/04/13(0.1.4.0):
*Fixed a bug where an item that could target Resurreviewy could only be used on humans by mistake.

*Resurrevi's nutritional consumption has been significantly reduced.

*Resurreviewy and Resurrevi not belonging to their own faction now heal much slower.

*Resurreviewy and Resurrevi that do not belong to their own faction no longer self-regenerate for a while when they go down.

*Resurreviewy and Resurrevi that do not belong to a faction and are still down can now be buried in a hole and extinguished.
Select a pawn to work with and right-click on the Resurreviewy to be buried in the hole to make the option appear.
Note that the speed of this operation depends on the mining skill, and you will also get a small amount of mining experience.

*New research has been added.

*New equipment has been added.
The new equipment can be equipped by all B.E.P. species, including LLittleFairy.

2023/03/27(0.1.3.0):
*Fixed some graphics

*Separated FacialAnimation definitions into separate mods
To reduce the load at startup, I have separated FacialAnimation images and definitions into separate mods.
Please subscribe from the collection.

*Resurreviewy's body color is now the same mold as my other race.
Therefore, Resurreviewy's body color has changed in the existing data.
I apologize for the inconvenience, but please use a character editor type mod to correct this.
sorry.

2023/03/05(0.1.2.0):
*Resurreviewy now appear dressed according to their roles

2023/01/31(0.1.1.4):
*Research race restrictions have been removed

*Added new equipment
Instead of adding the equipment of another race, this mod is now added by itself
Please note that you can no longer wear clothes of other races

*Armor values of various equipment have been adjusted

*Resurreviewy who appeared at the event could not be tamed, so this has been corrected so that he can be tamed by making her a wild man when he appears

2023/01/30(0.1.1.3):
*Various statuses are no longer corrected based on age

2023/01/29(0.1.1.2):
*Increased the number of hairstyle types to 8

2023/01/27(0.1.1.1):
*Separated horn color settings

2023/01/15(0.1.1.0):
*Architect categories have been merged

2023/01/08(0.1.0.4):
*The setting was changed so that the gene of Biotech's appearance system cannot be adapted

2023/01/06(0.1.0.3):
*Support for the function of fertility change through Biotech linkage of HAR

2022/11/23(0.1.0.1):
*Skin and hair colors are no longer changed by genes

*Adjusted behavior of source code

2022/11/13(0.1.0.0):
*Release.
</Resur.Update.label>


</LanguageData>